Papers of the National War Labor Board on Microfilm 5752 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Resumes of Cases continued; Examiners Reports (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Sizer Forge. Buffalo, NY, 89 (Reel 2)
  - Carpenters v. McDougall-Duluth Ship Yards. Duluth, MN, 90 (Reel 2)
  - Request of War Department for Opinion on Proposed Wage Scales for Licensed Deck and Engine Officers in the Atlantic and Gulf Service. N.A, 91 (Reel 2)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. Emergency Fleet. Philadelphia, 92 (Reel 2)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 137 v. Municipal Gas. Albany, NY, 93 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Western Chemical. Denver, 94 (Reel 2)
  - Pattern Workers v. General Electric et al. Fort Wayne, IN, 95 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Citizens Ice. Los Angeles, 96 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Jefferson Ice. Los Angeles, 97 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Union Ice. Los Angeles, 98 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Merchants Ice. Los Angeles, 99 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Ice Distributing. Los Angeles, 100 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 689 v. Washington Railway and Electric. Washington, DC, 101 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Louisville Gas and Electric. Louisville, KY, 102 (Reel 2)
  - Composition Roofers, Local 32 v. Master Slag and Composition Roofers. Philadelphia, 103 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Review Publishing. Spokane, WA, 104 (Reel 2)
  - Beaver Machine and Tool v. Employees. Newark, NJ, 105 (Reel 2)
  - Bill Posters and Billers v. A. Van Buren. New York City, 106 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Elwood, Anderson, and Lapel Railroad. Elwood, IN, 107 (Reel 2)
  - Fire Department v. City of Fort Dodge. Fort Dodge, IA, 108 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Alfred F. Moore. Philadelphia, 109 (Reel 2)
  - Building Trades Council et al. v. E.R. Squibb and Son. New Brunswick, NJ, 110 (Reel 2)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 62 v. M. and S. Railway and Light. Youngstown, OH, 111 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Scientific Glass. Vineland, NJ, 112 (Reel 2)
  - Utah Manufacturers Association v. Unions. Salt Lake City, UT, 113 (Reel 2)
  - Molders v. Lovell. Arlington, NJ, 114 (Reel 2)
  - S.H. Thompson Manufacturing v. Patternmakers. Dayton, OH, 115 (Reel 2)
  - Textile Workers v. Manufacturers Association. Fall River, MA, 116 (Reel 2)
  - Plumbers and Steam Fitters, Local 118 v. Du Pont Powder. Racine, WI, 117 (Reel 2)
  - Flour Mill Workers v. Listman Mill. La Crosse, WI, 118 (Reel 2)
  - Regan Printing v. Railway Mail Service. Chicago, 119 (Reel 2)
  - Box Makers and Sawyers, Local 1 v. Acme Box et al. Chicago, 120 (Reel 2)
  - Bucyrus Labor Union v. American Clay Working Machinery. Toledo, OH, 121 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Atlas Powder. Perryville, MD, 122 (Reel 2)
  - Waitresses, Local 810 v. Bethlehem Loading Plant. Mays Landing, NJ, 123 (Reel 2)
  - Carpenters District Council v. United States Cartridge. Lowell, MA, 124 (Reel 2)
  - I.S.O. and E., Local 45 v. City of Girard. Girard, KS, 125 (Reel 2)
  - Journeymen Tailors, Local 291 v. Employers. Newark, NJ, 126 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Liberty Mills. Nashville, TN, 127 (Reel 2)
  - Journeymen Plasterers, Local 32 v. Employers. Denver, 128 (Reel 2)
  - Central Labor Council v. Long Beach Paint and Paper. San Pedro and Wilmington, CA, 129 (Reel 2)
  - Waiters, Local 1 v. New York Restaurant Keepers. New York City, 130 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Nuncesser Carbon and Battery. Cleveland, 131 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. St. Joseph Lead. Flat River, MO, 132 (Reel 2)
  - Teamsters and Chauffeurs v. Ward Baking. New York City, 133 (Reel 2)
  - Machinists v. Wisconsin Tool and Supply. Milwaukee, Wi, 134 (Reel 2)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 703 v. St. Louis Electrical Terminal Railway. St. Louis, MO, 135 (Reel 2)
  - Jearl C. Idler v. Employer. Saint Mary's, OH, 136 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Buffalo and Depew Railway. Depew, NY, 137 (Reel 2)
  - Janitors, Local 14782 v. Employers. Chicago, 138 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Claude Fisher. Phoenix, AZ, 139 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Hoover Steel Ball. Ann Arbor, MI, 140 (Reel 2)
  - Typographical Union, Local 12 v. Newspaper Publishers. Baltimore, MD, 141 (Reel 2)
  - Metal Polishers, Local 57 v. Willys-Morrow et al. Elmira, NY, 142 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Lehigh Navigation Electric. Bethlehem, PA. Employees v. Columbia Wagon. Columbia, PA, 143 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Star Brass. Boston, 144 (Reel 2)
  - Love Brothers v. Molders. Aurora, IL, 145 (Reel 2)
  - Molders, Local 453 v. Employers. Hartford, CT, 146 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. United Alloy Steel Corporation. Canton, OH, 147 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Kranich and Bach. New York City, 148 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Employers. Bristol, PA, 149 (Reel 2)
  - Firemen v. City of Gary. Gary, IN, 150 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Ahanapee Veneering. Birchwood, WI, 151 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Prairie Pipe Line. Carrollton, MO, 152 (Reel 2)
  - John D. Lundquist v. Ridgway Dynamo and Engine. Ridgway, PA, 153 (Reel 2)
  - Metal Polishers vs. Bosh Magneto et al. Springfield and Chicopee, MA, 154 (Reel 2)
  - Molders v. McFarland Foundry et al. Trenton, NJ, 155 (Reel 2)
  - Metal Polishers v. Underwood Typewriter et al. N.A, 156 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Sharon Steel Hoop. Sharon, PA, 157 (Reel 2)
  - Request of W. Parranto for Complaint Blanks. Coffeyville, KS. Journeymen Tailors v. Guiterman Brothers. St. Paul, MN, 158 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Hercules Gas Engine Works et al. Evansville, IN, 159 (Reel 2)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 494 v. Employers. Spokane, WA, 160 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Appalachian Power. Bluefield, WV, 161 (Reel 2)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 360 v. Henry Mush and Armour. New York City, 162 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Ewart Furniture et al. Portsmouth, OH, 163 (Reel 2)
  - Machinists, Local 60 v. F. Joseph Lamb. Detroit, MI, 164 (Reel 2)
  - Molders, Local 84 v. Foundrymen. Buffalo, NY, 165 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Superior Door and Sash. Superior, WI, 166 (Reel 2)
  - Interurban Trainmen v. Toledo, Fostoria and Findlay Railway et al. Astoria, OH, 167 (Reel 2)
  - Fire Fighters, Local 82 v. City of Minneapolis. Minneapolis, MN, 168 (Reel 2)
  - Molders, Local 16 v. Granger et al. Louisville, KY., 169 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. American Rolling Mill. Middletown, OH, 170 (Reel 2)
  - Steam Flour Mill Operators, Local 441 v. Walnut Creek Flour Mill. Great Bend, KS, 171 (Reel 2)
  - Silk Manufacturers v. Textile Workers. Paterson, NJ., 172 (Reel 2)
  - Appeal by Western Union Employees from Award Made by Postmaster General. N.A, 173 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 256 v. Pacific Gas and Electric. Sacramento, CA., 174 (Reel 2)
    1p
  - Examiner Report--Unidentified Fragment., 175 (Reel 2)
  - Federal Labor Union 15543 et al. v. Hammond Lumber Company et al. Van Buren, ME., 176 (Reel 2)
    25 pp.
  - Steam Engineers, Local 45 et al. v. Joplin and Pittsburg Railway. Joplin, MO and Pittsburg, KS, 177 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland Railway. Cleveland., 178 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 26 v. Detroit United Railway. Detroit., 179 (Reel 2)
    30 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 168 v. Scranton Railway. Scranton, PA., 180 (Reel 2)
    13 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 576 v. Schenectady Railway. Schenectady, NY., 181 (Reel 2)
    6 pp.
  - Stove Mounters, Local 8 v. Estate Stove. Hamilton, OH., 182 (Reel 2)
    10 pp.
  - Painters Union 47 et al. v. Master House Painters et al. Indianapolis, IN., 183 (Reel 2)
    11 pp.
  - Boilermakers, Local 592 v. Kansas City Structural Steel et al. Tulsa, OK., 184 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 735 v. Jacksonville Traction. Jacksonville, FL., 185 (Reel 2)
    14 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 802 v. Kansas City and Western Railway. Leavenworth, KS., 186 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 194 v. New Orleans Railway and Light. New Orleans, LA., 187 (Reel 2)
    17 pp.
  - Federal Labor Union 16104 v. Emerson Brantingham Manufacturing et al. Batavia Illinois., 188 (Reel 2)
    7 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 515 v. Galesburg Railway, Lighting and Power. Galesburg, IL., 189 (Reel 2)
    8 pp.
  - Employees v. Red Star Milling et al. Wichita, KS., 190 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 282, 580, and 832 v. New York State Railways. Rochester, NY., 191 (Reel 2)
    4 pp.
  - Machinists, Local 330 v. Russell Motor Car. Buffalo, NY., 192 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. General Electric. Schenectady, NY., 193 (Reel 2)
  - Machinists, Local 1 v. Midvale Steel and Ordnance. Philadelphia., 194 (Reel 2)
    15 pp.
  - Textile Workers v. Lowell Mill Treasurers. Lowell, MA., 195 (Reel 2)
    12 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 806, 810 and 749 v. City Railway et al. Dayton, OH., 196 (Reel 2)
    9 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 623 v. International Railway. Buffalo, NY., 197 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 732 v. Georgia Railway and Power. Atlanta, GA., 198 (Reel 2)
    27 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland and Eastern Traction. Cleveland., 199 (Reel 2)
    5 pp.
  - Painters, Local 28 v. Gahogen Shipyards et al. Long Island City, NY., 200 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Middletown Car. Middletown, PA., 201 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 746 v. Denver City Tramway. Denver., 202 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. East St. Louis, Columbus, and Waterloo Railway. East St. Louis, IL., 203 (Reel 2)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 601 v. Hammong Packing et al. McKeesport and Pittsburgh, PA., 204 (Reel 2)
  - Metal Trades Council v. Ajax Iron Works et al. Denver., 205 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 618 v. Rhode Island Company. Providence, RI., 206 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 589 v. Boston Elevated Railway. Boston., 207 (Reel 2)
  - Leather Workers v. National Leather Belting et al. New York City., 208 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 725 v. Birmingham Railway, Light and Power. Birmingham, AL., 209 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 761 v. Springfield Consolidated. Springfield, IL., 210 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 669 v. Auburn and Syracuse Electric Railroad. Auburn, NY., 211 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 713 v. Memphis Street Railway. Memphis, TN., 212 (Reel 2)
    18 pp.
  - Conductors, Trainmen, and Engineers v. Interurban Lines. Portland, OR., 213 (Reel 2)
  - Railroad Trainmen, Lodge 808 et al. v. Pacific Electric Railway. Los Angeles., 214 (Reel 2)
    28 pp.
  - Machinists, Local 161 v. Kleiber-Dawson Machine. Indianapolis., 215 (Reel 2)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. American Sheet and Tin Plate. Ellwood, IN., 216 (Reel 2)
  - Laundry Workers, Local 36 v. Imperial Laundry et al. Little Rock, AR., 217 (Reel 2)
  - Machinists, Local 335 v. Connersville Blower et al. Connersville, IN., 218 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Eugene Dietzgen. Chicago., 219 (Reel 2)
    24 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 737 v. Northern Electric Railway. Syracuse, NY., 220 (Reel 2)
  - Molders, Local 307 v. Morgan Engineering. Alliance. OH., 221 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 767 v. Knoxville Railway and Light. Knoxville, TN., 222 (Reel 2)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, Local 386 et al. v. St. Louis Coffin. St. Louis, MO., 223 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Atlantic Elevator et al. Minneapolis, MN., 224 (Reel 2)
    37 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 764 v. Kansas City Railways. Kansas City, MO., 225 (Reel 2)
    42 pp.
  - Kansas City Railways' Employees v. Kansas City Railways. Kansas City, MO., 226 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 199 v. Ottumwa Railway. Ottumwa, IA., 227 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 381 v. Butte Electric Railway. Butte, MT., 228 (Reel 2)
  - Textile Workers v. Lorraine Mills et al. Pawtucket, RI et al., 229 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 669 and 737 v. Rochester and Syracuse Railway. Syracuse, NY. 9pp. Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 580 v. Syracuse and Suburban Railway. Syracuse, NY., 230 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 421 v. Shamokin and Mt. Carmel Transit. Mt. Carmel, PA., 231 (Reel 2)
  - Locomotive Engineers, Local 419 and 868 v. New York Consolidated. New York City., 232 (Reel 2)
    35 pp.
  - Molders, Local 62 v. Bass Foundry. Fort Wayne, IN., 233 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 681 and 737 v. Empire State Railroad. Syracuse, NY., 234 (Reel 2)
  - Steam Fitters, Local 572 et al. v. Nashville Munitions Plant. Nashville, TN., 235 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 441 v. Des Moines City Railway et al. Des Moines, IA., 236 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. Lima Street Lines. Lima, OH., 237 (Reel 2)
  - Textile Workers v. Swift Spinning Mills. Columbus, GA., 238 (Reel 2)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 834 v. Columbus Street Railway. Columbus, GA., 239 (Reel 2)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. George W. Smith et al. Philadelphia., 240 (Reel 2)
  - Machinists, Local 12 v. Poole Engineering. Baltimore, MD., 241 (Reel 2)
  - Employees v. A.H. Peterson Manufacturing. Milwaukee, WI., 242 (Reel 2)
- Examiners' Reports continued (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. A.H. Peterson Manufacturing. Milwaukee, WI., 1 (Reel 3)
  - Elevator Operators and Starters, Local 495 v. Employers. San Francisco, 2 (Reel 3)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 227 v. Armour. Louisville, KY., 3 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Standard Boiler and Plate Iron. Niles, OH., 4 (Reel 3)
  - Workers v. National Car Coupler. Attica, IN., 5 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists v. Niles-Bement-Pond. Plainfield, NJ., 6 (Reel 3)
  - Interurban Trainmen v. Danville, Urbana, and Champaign Railway et al. Joliet and Springfield, IL., 7 (Reel 3)
  - Boilermakers, Local 127 v. Advance Rumley. Battle Creek, MI, 8 (Reel 3)
  - Foundry Employees, Local 66 et al. v. Baker Manufacturing. Saratoga Springs, NY., 9 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists v. American Locomotive Works. Paterson, NJ., 10 (Reel 3)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 312 313 and 599 v. Tri-City Railway et al. Davenport, IA., 11 (Reel 3)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 752 v. Bloomington and Normal Railway. Bloomington, IL., 12 (Reel 3)
  - Molders, Local 277 v. Niles-Bement-Pond et al. Ridgway, PA., 13 (Reel 3)
  - Molders v. Hyde Windlass. Bath, ME., 14 (Reel 3)
  - Molders, Local 183 v. Employers. Williamsport, PA., 15 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Detroit Forging. Detroit., 16 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Five Employers. Chambersburg, PA., 17 (Reel 3)
  - Molders, Local 420 v. Elkhart Iron Works et al. Elkhart, IN., 18 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists v. Sturtevant. Hyde Park, MA., 19 (Reel 3)
  - Coopers v. Sinclair Refining. Coffeyville, KS., 20 (Reel 3)
  - Blacksmiths v. Bedford Stone Club. Bedford, IN., 21 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists, Local 1 v. J.G. Brill et al. Philadelphia., 22 (Reel 3)
  - Discharged Employees v. Bethlehem Steel. North Lebanon, PA, 23 (Reel 3)
  - Typographical Union 16 v. American Newspaper Publishers. Chicago, IL., 24 (Reel 3)
  - Conductors and Motormen v. Michigan United Railways. Jackson, MI., 25 (Reel 3)
    16 pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati, Lawrenceburg, and Aurora Electric Railway. Cincinnati, OH., 26 (Reel 3)
    20 pp.
  - Blacksmiths, Local 455 v. Evansville Tool Works. Evansville, IN., 27 (Reel 3)
  - Tin, Steel, and Granite Workers Union 10943 v. National Enameling and Stamping. Granite City, IL., 28 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Scranton Bolt and Nut. Scranton, PA., 29 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Eastern Steel. Pottsville, PA., 30 (Reel 3)
    29 pp.
  - Employees v. Bethlehem Steel and Lebanon Valley Iron. Lebanon, PA., 31 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Burden Iron and Steel. Troy, NY., 32 (Reel 3)
  - Molders, Local 395 v. Aetna Foundry et al. Warren, OH., 33 (Reel 3)
  - Labor v. Detroit Employers Association. Detroit, 34 (Reel 3)
  - Association of Employing Printers v. Printing Pressmen's and Assistant's Union, Local 23, New York City., 35 (Reel 3)
    34 pp.
  - Boiler Makers, Local 295 v. Stacy Schmidt. York, PA., 36 (Reel 3)
  - Twin City Carpenters v. Employers. Minneapolis, MN., 37 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Maryland Pressed Steel. Hagerstown, MD., 38 (Reel 3)
    19 pp.
  - Steam and Operating Engineers, Local 567 v. Ohio Electric Railway and Power. Zanesville, OH., 39 (Reel 3)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers, Local 81 v. Wheeling Steel and Iron. Wheeling, WV., 40 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Commonwealth Steel. Granite City, IL., 41 (Reel 3)
  - Gas Makers v. Minneapolis Gas Light. Minneapolis, MN., 42 (Reel 3)
  - Molders, Local 11 v. Rochester Foundrymen's Association. Rochester, NY., 43 (Reel 3)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 65 and 122 v. Employers. Great Falls, MT., 44 (Reel 3)
  - Flour and Cereal Workers, Union 16302 v. Washburn Crosby et al. Minneapolis, MN., 45 (Reel 3)
  - Boiler Makers, Local 83 v. Kansas City Structural Steel. Kansas City and Argentine, KS., 46 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists, Local 459 v. Minnesota Manufacturing Association. St. Paul, MN., 47 (Reel 3)
  - Central Trades and Labor Assembly et al. v. New York Air Brake. Watertown, NY., 48 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists, Lodge 55 v. Superior Tool and Die et al. Columbus, OH., 49 (Reel 3)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 101 v. Aberthaw Construction. Sparrows Point, MD., 50 (Reel 3)
  - Engineers, Firemen, and Switchmen v. Garfield Smelting. Salt Lake City, UT, 51 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists v. Harrisburg Boiler and Manufacturing. Harrisburg, PA., 52 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Stockyards. South St. Paul, MN., 53 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. American Hide and Leather et al. Sheboygan, WI., 54 (Reel 3)
    97 pp.
  - Employees v. S.B. Stine. Osceola Mills, PA., 55 (Reel 3)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. Carpenter Steel et al. Reading, PA., 56 (Reel 3)
  - Iron Workers, Local 10 v. Builders Association. Kansas City, MO., 57 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists v. Winslow Brothers. Chicago, IL., 58 (Reel 3)
  - Carpenters District Council v. Contractors. Denver., 59 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Great Western manufacturing. Laporte, IN, 60 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Matthews Engineering. Sandusky, OH., 61 (Reel 3)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. Pitman and Brown et al. Salem, MA, 62 (Reel 3)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 532 v. Montana Power. Billings, MT., 63 (Reel 3)
  - Printing Pressmen's Union 17 et al. v. Union Employing Printers' Association. Indianapolis, IN., 64 (Reel 3)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, Local 33 v. Famous Players, Lasky Corporation. Los Angeles., 65 (Reel 3)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 44 v. Rochester Light and Power. Rochester, NY. Employees and Machinists v. Midwest Engine. Indianapolis., 66 (Reel 3)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 125 v. Portland Railway, Light and Power. Portland, OR., 67 (Reel 3)
    33 pp.
  - Machinists, Local 459 v. St. Paul Foundry. St. Paul, MN., 68 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists, Local 459 v. American Hoist and Derrick. St. Paul, MN., 69 (Reel 3)
  - Molders, Local 386 v. Huber Manufacturing et al. Marion, OH, 70 (Reel 3)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 122 v. Montana Power et al. Great Falls, MT., 71 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Parlin and Orendorff. Canton, IL., 72 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists v. Burke and James. Chicago, IL., 73 (Reel 3)
  - Tin Smiths and Metal Workers v. Perkins Marine Lamp et al. Brooklyn, NY., 74 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. American and British Manufacturing. Providence, RI., 75 (Reel 3)
  - Pattern Makers v. Employers. Buffalo, NY., 76 (Reel 3)
  - Journeymen Plumbers v. Master Plumbers. Grand Rapids, MI, 77 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Union Electric Light and Power. St. Louis, MO, 78 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Westinghouse Electric. Lester, PA., 79 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. William Brothers Boiler Manufacturing. Minneapolis, MN, 80 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Ross Gear and Tool. Lafayette, IN., 81 (Reel 3)
    36 pp.
  - Molders, Local 205 v. Newark Stamping and Foundry. Newark, OH., 82 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Richmond Light and Power. Staten Island, NY, 83 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Timken Roller Bearing. Canton, OH, 84 (Reel 3)
  - Newspaper Publishers v. Machinists. New York City., 85 (Reel 3)
  - Wyoming Valley metal Trades v. Vulcan Iron Works et al. Wilkes-Barre, PA., 86 (Reel 3)
  - Leather Workers, Local 89 v. William F. Mosser et al. Richmond, VA., 87 (Reel 3)
  - Molders v. Huntington Steel Foundry, Huntington, IN., 88 (Reel 3)
  - Machinists v. Smith Drum. Philadelphia., 89 (Reel 3)
  - Molders v. Blake-Knowles Pump Works. East Cambridge, MA., 90 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Wayne Works. Richmond, IN., 91 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Swayne-Robinson. Richmond, IN., 92 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. American Seeding Machine. Richmond, IN., 93 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Richmond Casket. Richmond, IN, 94 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. F.N. Watt. Richmond, IN., 95 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Standard Pattern Manufacturing. Richmond, IN., 96 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Davis Motor Car. Richmond, IN., 97 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. F. and N. Lawn Mower. Richmond, IN., 98 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Pilot Motor Car. Richmond, IN., 99 (Reel 3)
  - Firemen v. City of Richmond. Richmond, IN., 100 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Miller-Kemper. Richmond, IN., 101 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Hayes Track Appliance. Richmond, IN., 102 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Starr Piano. Richmond, IN., 103 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. J.M. Hutton. Richmond, IN, 104 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. National Automatic Tool. Richmond, IN., 105 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Dille-McQuire Manufacturing. Richmond, IN, 106 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Richmond Safety Gate. Richmond, IN., 107 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Jenkins Vulcan Spring. Richmond, IN., 108 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. W.N. Johnson Auto Sheet Metal. Richmond, IN., 109 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Louck and Hill Furniture. Richmond, IN., 110 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Richmond Malleable Iron. Richmond, IN., 111 (Reel 3)
  - Employees v. Simplex Tool. Richmond, IN., 112 (Reel 3)
  - Pattern Makers v. Banner Pattern. Columbus, OH., 113 (Reel 3)
  - Pattern Makers v. Melvin Brothers Pattern. Columbus, OH., 114 (Reel 3)
  - Die Sinkers v. Western Drop Forge. Marion, IN., 115 (Reel 3)
  - Blacksmiths' Union v. La Crosse Plow. La Crosse, WI., 116 (Reel 3)
  - Brick Layers, Local 7 v. Tri-City Masonry Contractors. Rock Island, Il., 117 (Reel 3)
  - Mineral Workers, Local 253 v. International Agricultural Corporation. Mulberry, FL., 118 (Reel 3)
  - Mineral Workers, Local 253 v. American Agricultural Chemical. Pierce, FL., 119 (Reel 3)
- Examiners' Reports continued; Findings and Awards (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Hayes Pump and Planter. Galva, IL, 1 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. American Can. Haywood, IL., 2 (Reel 4)
  - Coopers v. Sellig et al. Chicago., 3 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists v. Crocker Wheeler et al. Newark, NJ., 4 (Reel 4)
  - Steel Workers v. Athenia Steel and Wire. Athenia, NJ., 5 (Reel 4)
    26 pp.
  - Commercial Telegraphers, Local 47 v. United Press Association. New York City., 6 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists, Local 1004 v. Benjamin Iron and Steel. Hazleton, PA., 7 (Reel 4)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 286 v. United Gas and Electric. New Albany, IN., 8 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. American Locomotive. Richmond, VA., 9 (Reel 4)
  - Fire Fighters, Local 87 v. City of Jackson. Jackson, MS., 10 (Reel 4)
  - Savannah Electric v. Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 856. Savannah, GA., 11 (Reel 4)
  - Butterick Publishing v. Franklin Union 23 et al. New York City., 12 (Reel 4)